

# MIGUEL PINTO

JUNIOR FRONTEND
DEVELOPER

# CONTACT

- migueljcpinto@gmail.com
- Annette-von-Aretin Str.7 81737

  Munich
- +49 (0) 172 6740488
- (îm) <u>linkedin.com/in/migueljcpinto</u>
- github.com/MiketheBite

# **TECH SKILLS**

- JavaScript ES8+
- React.js
- HTML5
- CSS3
- MongoDB
- Node.js
- Next.js
- Git Workflow
- Figma (Basics)

#### **LANGUAGES**

- Portuguese Native
- German working language
- English Good knowledge
- Spanish Good knowledge

#### **HOBBIES**

Laufen, Schwimmen, CrossFit, Kino und Reisen

## PERSONAL PROFILE

Passionate about healthcare and digital technology, I have advanced my career as a nurse while simultaneously cultivating my interest in web development. With my skills as an analytical, task-oriented problem solver and my experience collaborating in multidisciplinary teams as an ICU nurse, I can make a valuable contribution. I am excited about new opportunities and look forward to creating positive impacts together.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Trainee Web Development**

Neuefische I School and Pool for digital talent Intensive Coding-Bootcamp in Part-time - 540 Hours Final project- <u>Team Up</u> 2023

# **Health Care and Nursing**

Interdisciplinary intensive care unit Clinic rechts der Isar, Munich 2018 - Currently

Stroke Unit/IMC Nursing Clinic rechts der Isar, Munich 2015 - 2018

Neurological nursing - Stroke Unit Nordwest Hospital, Frankfurt am Main 2012 - 2015

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Bootcamp Web Development**

Neuefische - March 2023 - September 2023 School and Pool for Digital Talent

Part-time intensive coding bootcamp

# Wound Expert ICW

Training

Clinic rechts der Isar 2020 - 2021

#### **Special Nursing Stroke-Unit**

Training

University Medicine of the Johannes Gutenberg University, Mainz 2014 - 2015

#### **Bachelor of Science in Nursing**

Bachelor

Nursing School Coimbra, Portugal 2007 - 2011

